that's me... highest
sales in the division.
And then in the morning I'm flying
back to omaha. That's great.
Coming through behind you.
Everything good out here?
Yeah. No. I'm fine.
I'm just starving. It's $10.50.
Oh. right.
Here you go.
Oh. and. darlin'. you keep the change.
And...
This one's for you.
well. thank you...
But I can't.
It's policy.
keep rockin'
love. love. love. love. love
love. love. love. love. love. love
I think you can maybe.
I hope it is maybe
but if we don't feel it
now. we never will. baby
Excuse me. darlin'.
Hello. beautiful.
Pretty drink for a pretty lady?
Sure.
Cheers.
Oh. now you are thirsty. aren't ya?
Whoo! Well. aren't you
just the sweetest thing?
Thanks. buddy.
Gotta jet.
Love. love. love. love. love.
love. love. love. love. love
Is that so?
I think you can maybe
I hope it is maybe
but if we don't feel it
now. we never will. baby
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm
Aw. come on.
Can't get rid of me that easily.
Any inside tips?
Hey. where ya headin' to?
Any good parties?
'cause I got a few hours
that I would love...
to kill.
Yeah. good luck with that.
You sure are a pretty
little thing. aren't ya?
gross.
Back off. or I'll vom.
Ohh.
Whoa.
Why am I trippin'?
what was in that drink?
Oh. just somethin' to make
ya a little bit friendlier.
We are friends. aren't we?
Ohh.
Come on. baby.
Just a little kiss.
Ohh. back off. creepo.
You good?
A-okay.
You are very naughty.
Hmm?
Left without saying good-bye.
Oh.
Don't you know when a
girl's playing hard to get?
What do you want?
Just one little kiss.
Mmm.
mmm.
Mm.
This is so gonna be viral.
Hey.
What about me?
Okay.
Let's get you out of here.
You're pretty.
I saw you eat some dude's face.
It was amazing.
Oh. that's just terrific.
Let's go. Come on.
I'll take you somewhere safe.
Bye-bye.
Mr.
Smiley face.
Addidc7ed.
Com
Adriano_CSI
Hey!
You finally decided to show.
So what do we got here?
Uh. male. mid-30s.
No I.D.
. just a room key for the hotel.
Woman found him over an hour ago.
I'd say. uh. that's it for witnesses.
Any cameras in here? Busted.
Checking on the garages.
Mm.
Jesus.
What the hell happened to him?
Look. uh. you wanna give us
a little space here. frank?
Yeah. frank.
Why don't you go canvas or something?
You got it.
Thanks. man.
The vic's human.
Yeah.
The killer definitely wasn't.
Well. our side?
I hope not.
This is sloppy. leaving a
feed behind like this.
I don't recognize this kind of kill.
You?
No. but it's a good way to die.
I mean. the dude died
with a smile on his face.
Hair.
Brunette.
Huh.
Got it.
What you got?
He's been drinking.
And I smell a human on him...
Female.
Well. at this time of
night. that combo...
My money's on the hotel bar.
Mm-hmm.
I don't know.
Sounds like a guy that was here.
But it's been a crazy. busy night.
I can't remember 'em all. you know.
liked the ladies. though.
How is that? I don't know.
Kept hitting on our bartender all night.
Leaves sniffing after
some little blonde.
This bartender... is she a
brunette by any chance?
Yeah. Name's bo.
She just started. like. a week ago.
You know. she's smokin' hot.
Huh. So you got a
last name. address?
No. no.
She's daily... or was.
You know. she leaves
on a bathroom break.
Don't ever come back.
She's totally fired now.
Rush the security
tape from the garage.
Our eyes only.
I want to get a look at this bo.
Gotcha.
hot sweat. got debt
keep your licker in the locker
'cause you don't know yet.
but I know what I am
they know what they are. so let me be
shipshape. ticker tape
looks to me like a narrow escape
but I know what I am.
they know what they are
so let me be
but it's all right. it's okay
I got the time. but
the time don't pay
it's all right. it's okay
I got the time. but
the time don't pay
it's all right. it's okay
I got the time. but
the time don't pay
it's all right
it's okay
I know what I am. they
know what they are
so let me be
Nice place while it lasted.
Shit.
Sorry.
I was just leaving.
Where am I?
Who are you?
Okay. just calm down.
You're okay.
You passed out last night.
Would've dropped you home.
But none of these wallets
appear to be yours.
That's a nice little
sideline you got going.
I'm a collector of rare wallets.
I'm not judging.
I'm glad you're okay.
I-I don't... I don't feel okay.
What happened last night?
Did... did somebody slip me something?
Yeah. some creep from the
bar spiked your drink.
And you hallucinated a lot
of weird stuff. I bet.
So you didn't...
So you didn't eat some dude's face
In an elevator? No.
There was no eating of faces.
wow. that's crazy.
Thank god!
That was some creepy ass shit.
mmm.
Mmm.
kids and your camera phones.
ohh.
Ohh.
Don't freak out.
I'm freaking out.
What did I just say?
How can I not freak out?
Have you seen you? Yes.
Did you kill him?
just slow down.
Oh. my god. Are you gonna kill me?
Oh. my god.
You know. that is just stupid.
Why... why would I save you...
Are you okay?
I don't know.
Can you just get asthma?
I think I'm totally
getting asthma here.
Just breathe.
Fine.
I don't need this.
I have to blow town now
after saving your ass
And find somewhere else to live...
Again.
You're welcome. by the way.
Excuse me. lady...
Person.
It's bo.
Hi.
Kenzi.
Look. I'm sorry.
You... you're obviously very nice for...
Whatever you are. um.
but I just had. like.
The scariest. weirdest
night of my life. okay.
So can just please talk about
this like normal people?
I think it's fairly clear that
I'm not exactly normal. Good.
Good. because normal people
do not help out strangers.
If you were normal.
I could be dead.
I won't tell anyone. Please.
I totally promise. okay?
Just... just give me. like. 20 minutes.
20 minutes. and you
will never. ever. ever
Have to ever see me ever again.
Please.
That depends.
Do you like milk shakes?
Gotcha.
gotcha.
gotcha. gotcha.
Hey. hey. hey.
Got it.
that the bartender?
Heading to her car.
With the blonde still
alive and kicking.
Now look. that's the part I don't get.
Why take the kid?
What did she want. a snack
for the road. what?
I think she was protecting her.
Hotel put a name to our john doe.
So I pulled his jacket.
He's got a few assaults.
He likes slipping things
into girls' drinks.
I'm thinking he targeted the blonde.
And the bartender stopped him.
Can you make that plate?
please.
Good. Put out an a.
P.B.
Maintain surveillance
but do not approach.
I want us to be first on the scene.
You got it.
and I'm-a draggin' them
around town. makin'
such a sad sound. baby
Are you just gonna stare at me?
Mnh. Sorry.
By the way. um. I know
things could've gotten
Really messed up for me last night
If you hadn't shown up. so...
Thanks.
Oh. well. um...
You're welcome.
Okay. uh... Screw it.
I gotta know.
Some things are too stupid
To say out loud. so...
but the booze dried up
and the car won't start
Here.
and I'm not done
You are a tool.
And I don't know
What the hell I am.
Honestly.
Just a freak. I guess.
Does it matter?
Kinda.
I mean. what exactly
did you do to him?
It's hard to explain. okay?
I just... I sort of. um...
I sort of drain people.
Oh. my god.
Are you a...
Dude. are you a frickin' vampire?
No. No. No.
It's not like that. okay?
It has nothing to do with blood.
It's...
It's just...
It's this...
hunger that builds and builds.
And then eventually I...
Do what I did last night.
So you can't control it?
No.
Wow.
That's shitty.
No. I'm serious.
That's. like. no way to live.
You should. uh. you should
really work on that.
Thanks.
So. look. are we done
with this show-and-tell?
'cause I gotta get going.
Can I get you anything else?
No. we're good.
...Goes down all cinnamon
brown. I'm moving on
I'm... I'm a little short right now.
If there's. uh.
Any way I could come
back some other time
And make it up to you...
God.
yes.
Whoa. whoa. whoa.
Hold up. woman!
What... what theell was that?
No. I'm serious!
What was that?
Oh. my god.
Mmm.
How's the tea?
Ahh. Always the best.
Always the best.
Ahh.
You know. when I walked
in here. that waitress...
She was seriously clockin' you. man.
And she looks just like your type.
I'm sure she does.
Mm-hmm.
Excuse me.
I'm gonna take my game on the road.
you do that.
Uh-huh. I'll show you
how it's done. baby.
Hello. hello. hello. hello.
The girl from last night... is it her?
You tell me.
Female. out-of-towner. unannounced...
Awfully friendly with humans.
It's beginning then.
I can try and stop this.
How?
Well. I'm not gonna kill her.
But there are ways of
making someone disappear.
No.
What's meant to be must be.
We can't fight fate.
Well. you can.
What do you want me to do?
Watch and wait.
I'll help how I can
when the time comes.
Hale. Mm-hmm.
Good job.
Okay. we're on our way.
Got a call on the car.
Let's shake.
Let's... Shake.
Don't worry about it.
It's on the house.
You sure? Thank you. Keep it warm. please.
You're saying you can seduce
people into doing anything
Just by touching them?
Sorta. It wears off and takes
a lot out of me. but yeah.
Yet you're broke. you
live in a crack shack.
And you run from town to town?
What are you doing wrong. girl?
God. that is no life for a sex superhero.
you know.
I think I liked you better
when you were scared of me.
No. what you need is
some kind of manager.
I nominate me.
Shocking. and no. thanks.
Give me a chance.
We would make a good team.
Okay.
Whoa.
Look. this isn't a joke. okay?
Has it occurred to you
That hanging out with
a homicidal freak
Might not be the brightest move for you?
Has it occurred to you
That I'm capable of making
that decision for myself?
"homicidal freak.
" god. you are so emo.
Excuse me?
Learn to enjoy your shit already.
You can frickin' control
people by touch.
And not in a creepy hand job way.
That is awesome!
Fine.
Let's say I take you with me.
What's in it for you?
Out here? Survival.
Mama always said.
"find the toughest kid
on the playground
And make friends with them.
You are definitely the toughest kid
On this playground.
And it would kick ass to be your friend.
I don't know.
Come on.
Every superhero needs a partner.
Let me be your robin.
I'll think about it.
Take them.
Here we go.
Aah.
Ohh.
kenzi. what's wrong?
Where are we taking her?
To the ash.
He insists on an audience.
Sucks to be her.
Guys. seriously. where
is my friend. huh?
Where is my friend?
okay. just
take off the hood.
You're a squirmish one. huh?
Oh. you guys have no idea what
you are dealing with here.
Okay.
Okay. just take off the hood!
Calm down!
I'm not saying anything
without my lawyer. Ohh.
Lawyer?
I know my rights. assholes.
is she serious?
Come on.
What is this place. huh?
I don't understand your obstinacy.
You know the rules.
Just name your clan.
Buddy. for the last time.
I don't have a clan. okay?
Or bagpipes or haggis.
I'm not frickin' scottish.
I mean. what
the hell kind of cops
Are you people. anyway. huh? Wh-what is this place?
I'm starting to think she's not faking.
Fakin' it?
Oh. that's... that's great.
Child...
Do you truly not know what you are?
What am I?
Forget about me.
What the hell are you?
I'm sorry. It's the morrigan.
She insists on seeing her.
You are not invited.
I know. and I'm hurt.
Cut the shit.
Word has that somebody's
kill was improperly dumped
In your territory last night.
And not by a local.
It'd be nice to know if we
had a new player in town.
We're handling it.
I don't speak to the help.
Hi. Yeah. hello?
Could somebody please just tell me
What the hell's going on here?
Lauren. take her to the lab.
grab her.
Aah!
Enough!
Lauren needs to examine the girl.
Please...
Come with me.
You and I need to talk.
because I'm your cousin.
And I'm in trouble. you dick.
Yeah. I know your friggin'
connections. okay.
You want these wallets?
Trace that plate for me.
Or I'm telling your mom
you're being mean.
asshole.
So what are you checking me for?
Brands.
Ritual scarring.
The different clans mark themselves
In different ways.
My god. you're beautiful.
I meant that professionally.
It's cool.
I. uh...
I kind of have that effect on people.
Aha. Well. that would fit
my hypothesis on you.
Mm-hmm?
Would you mind if I ask you some
incredibly personal questions?
Well. all questions
feel kinda personal
When you're commando.
Right.
Sorry.
Uh. please.
I'll. um...
I'll answer yours.
If you answer mine.
What the hell were those
freaks that I just met?
They're fae...
An evolutionary branch
that predates on humans.
So am I fae?
Yes. Well...
That's your genus. not your species.
And for those of us
who flunked biology?
I meant...
Fae is a general classification.
There are many different types.
So what type are you?
The insatiably curious
human doctor type.
I'm in it for the science.
Oh. kinky.
Now for the million-dollar question.
What kind of fae am I?
The girl doesn't even know she's fae.
She's as ignorant as a human.
so are you
if you believe her.
Oh. come on.
I mean. listen to yourself.
You're not seriously suggesting
That she's been hidden
from us since birth?
I'm suggesting we need to be
united in how we deal with this.
Little problem.
I'm not much of a team player.
If word gets out we've had a
free fae under our noses.
We'll be the laughingstock of the counties.
Well. then it's agreed.
Let's just kill the little bitch and be done with it.
It would be wiser to wait.
Tell me...
Was your neutering...
Ceremonial or a birth defect?
Her freedom is dangerous to us both.
She cannot be allowed to
exist in between our sides.
Which is why we need to make
her choose between us...
The old way.
I examined your kill from
last night. and based
On your feeding signature. you're...
Just say it.
You're a succubus.
A succubus?
Mm.
Can you fix it?
well. there's
nothing to fix.
You're a perfect biological specimen
Of your kind.
Who has a habit of waking
up next to dead lovers.
I mean. if that's not sick.
Then I would like a second opinion.
We can help you learn to
control it. if you like.
That's possible? Definitely.
If you'd been born into a clan.
You would've been taught how by now.
You'd still have to feed.
But you wouldn't always have to kill.
You deserve a normal life. and
we can offer that to you.
What's the catch?
The fae are divided...
The light and the dark.
I presume they'd want
you to join one of them
Before they'd allow me
to offer you much help.
I can offer you things...
If we get out of here.
I know what you're doing.
Do you want me to stop?
No.
You didn't think it was gonna
be that easy. did you?
A girl can dream. can't she?
Hands. please.
Sorry.
Had to try.
No. Good. No.
It was. uh. very informative.
Where are you taking her?
The glass factory.
Why?
It's neutral territory.
They're gonna give her the test.
Without training?
That's madness.
It's not our call.
'allo. Privet.
Did you get it?
Wait.
Hold on. hold on. hold on.
Okay.
"providence glass. inc.
On front.
Thank you.
Owe you one. Bye.
okay.
Party at the glass factory.
that's not weird.
Ew. Pardon the
turkish prison chic.
It's a little obvious for my taste.
We can manage chairs at least.
We're civilized folk.
By the way. congrats on
your amnesia girl routine.
You've got everybody buying it.
But between you and I.
You know more than you're
telling. don't you?
Do you?
Okay.
A girl's gotta have her mystery.
I can respect that.
I'm sorry.
Not to interrupt your. um. crazy.
But who are you?
Local governme..
Consider me the welcome wagon
For the dark fae.
Do you know why you've
been brought here today?
You're gonna be tested.
Oh. wow.
Will there be math?
funny.
She's funny.
Listen here. norma fae.
We have a millennia-old
2-party system.
And it works just swell.
Because membership is mandatory.
Well. I must have lost my invitation.
Which is a problem.
You see. you running around
free and nonpartisan
Gives all the little lemmings ideas.
I don't want any trouble. okay.
Promise.
Just let me go.
Well. lucky for you. if you
survive your test today.
You'll have the opportunity
to join a side.
Problem solved.
Join?
Why the hell would I want to do that?
We take care of our own.
We'll place you in a human occupation
That is to our advantage.
Help with the disposal of your kills.
Et cetera. et cetera.
Oh!
And dental.
Well. I'll keep that in mind.
You should.
I hear you've been
alone for a long time.
No friends or family.
Afraid you'd kill them. I'd imagine.
Sounds lonely.
You have the chance
To be a part of something now...
A chance to have a new family...
Or to have enemies.
So...
Be very careful how you
play the next few hours.
welcome to the top
of the food chain. doll.
Enjoy it while it lasts.
So what exactly am I
in for here. huh?
Big. bad nasties?
The loch ness monster?
Underfae.
Under what now?
Underfae... those of our kind
that don't exactly fit
In the human world.
Very old. very dangerous.
You'll face two.
Well. what are my chances?
I wouldn't bet on you.
Have I spit in your coffee or something?
What is your deal?
Kiss me. wow. are
you bad at reading women.
we
don't have time for this.
You need all of the strength you
can get. so take some of mine.
Won't I kill you?
Just kiss me.
Oh!
Ohh.
ohh.
Wow.
did you... did you feel that?
That was like... that was
like the 4th of July
In my mouth.
Hey.
You stopped me.
No one's ever opped me before.
Fae are different than humans.
Your powers won't work
the same on all of us.
Well. how am I supposed to
beat these guys?
You'll be faster.
You'll be smarter.
They're gonna underestimate you.
Use that to your advantage.
I misjudged you.
You got any other advice?
Don't get dead.
And you're back to being an asshole.
That's nice.
I was not expecting thunderdome.
He's big. but he's slow.
These are your weapons.
Choose wisely.
Good luck.
Uhh!
Aah!
Enough!
To the death.
What are they feeding you down here?
Aah!
She's probably in there having tea.
Ohh.
Please don't be rats.
Ugh.
Aah!
Gross.
ohh.
Hello.
Hi.
Would you like some tea?
What just happened?
I thought we could use some privacy.
Please...
Sit down.
We don't have much time.
I want to help you.
How?
I'm a pain eater.
Let me take yours.
I can end your suffering.
If you'll trust me.
Hello?
okay.
I'd like to show you something.
Those are your dead.
I-I-I don't want to be here anymore.
I don't want to see this.
That's all you've been
doing. ten long years...
Killing and running.
Aren't you tired?
Yes.
How many more will have
to die so you can live?
No.
No. it's not like that anymore.
I-I know what I really am.
They told me that I can
learn how to fight it.
You don't actually
believe that. do you?
You're an abomination. child.
You know it in your heart.
Do the right thing.
Oh. bo.
But I don't know what the
right thing is anymore.
Can you help me?
If you're willing.
What is it?
Your way out.
You'll sleep
And never wake up.
No.
I-I don't know.
It will be quick and beautiful.
A gesture of love.
No one will even miss you.
No one will mourn you.
Nobody needs you.
bo. wake up!
bo. wake up. damn it!
Bo. wake up.
Wake up!
Bo. he's killing you!
Drink.
bo!
Drink!
Bo! Bo!
Let me go. you big lug head!
Bo!
Bo. wake up!
Drink!
No.
no.
Get out of my head. you freak.
Help!
Oh!
she's mine.
This one has passed the test.
It has been witnessed.
Child. you may name your side.
Neither!
I choose humans.
Now can we kill her?
She passes without any training.
Who is this girl?
May I offer an opinion?
You have no station here. old man.
Don't you have some shoes to cobble
Or a garden to decorate?
Someone...
Hid her from both our sides.
It would be wise to learn why and who
Before killing her.
Great. And in the meantime.
she could expose us all.
Not without exposing herself.
I'm not saying there won't be a time
When she needs to be put down.
I'm saying. choose it wisely.
I feel like we've been paroled.
You sort of have been.
Any conditions on our release?
No more evidence for humans to find.
No messing in fae business.
And no more leaving town.
The elders want you where
they can watch you.
Well. they don't own me. and I'm
not very good at being obedient.
Learn.
And when you need
help... if I need help.
When you need help.
You can find me at the 39th division.
And. bo?
You did well.
I knew I smelled popo.
I'm not crazy. right?
That all just happened?
yep.
And now we know... anyone could be fae.
My bet's on wiener dude.
So...
What now?
We go home and we figure
out the rest tomorrow.
"we." huh?
I gotta figure out some way to
make a living while I'm here.
And you're the one who
thought we'd be a good team.
So yeah. "we.
Cool. Just so we're clear
about this partnership.
You be you and all. uh. but
I'm only into guys. Sorry.
I'll try to
contain my disappointment.
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm